### **About Me**

User interface and graphic designer, I've been in the design space for over a decade now and have found myself working on a wide range of projects, for a number of interesting clients both national and international.

For the last 5 years I have been part of product development in one way or the other, working alongside everyone from developers, product owners, and stakeholders to deliver modern user interfaces and product identities.

I've learnt a great deal in working fast and lean, using methodologies like agile, design sprints, and user centred design. Time spent with user research and testing methods, as well as front end development, allow me enough common sense and knowledge to be considered dangerous.

Outside of professional life I enjoy art & design in general (which helps inspiration), am learning to draw, enjoy CrossFit, love music, video gamer and cinephile.

## **Experience**

Freelance // Graphic Designer Milton Keynes // February 2020 - Present

Taking a step back to rekindle working with, and loving, design again.

Worked with clients to understand design briefs and requirements. Developed artwork to branding guidelines, ready for print and digital output whilst liasing with both internal and external departments in order to complete work to tight deadlines.

**Aiimi //** UX Designer London // July 2019 - January 2020

Made the transition to a solely UX Designer where it was my responsibility to gather an understanding of how users of Aiimi's InsightMaker product were finding difficulties and/or requirements for features where friction arose.

This feedback and research would then help product owners and devlopers to better understand what we could potentially deliver in order to improve standing with, and delight, the end users.

Day to day work would revolve around user testing session, user feedback gathering, prototyping, workflow design, and wireframing.

As part of Aiimi we ran 5 day design sprints, both internally, and externally with clients where I acted as UX consultant.

# Background

- User interface
- User experience
- Product design
- Accessibility
- Web design
- Mobile-first and responsive
- Front end development
- Email marketing
- · Graphic design
- Logos and branding
- Packaging
- Brochures and catalogues
- Exhibition graphics

### **Software & Tools**

- Sketch
- InVision
- Figma
- Photoshop
- Illustrator
- InDesign
- Xd
- HTML and CSS coding
- Office Suite & Google Docs
- JIRA
- · GIT

### Education

HND Graphic Design & Communication

Milton Keynes College

**WorkForce Software** // UI & Graphic Designer Milton Keynes // July 2016 - June 2019

Workplace Systems was aquired by WorkForce Software in Summer 2016, leading to us becoming a global team spanning from Sydney, Australia to the United States.

In mid-2018 the company decided to refocus their product offerings into a new, fully integrated suite of products that took from the lessons we had learnt in the 20+ years of schedule software. I was lucky enough to be a key member of the product group leading this venture and took onboard the duties of defining the user interface for this new product, as well as lend support on the user experience requirements.

Visited customers and users in numerous locations around Europe for research purposes, requirement gathering, and even in a consultancy role whilst assisting Product Owners and the sales team.

Embedded within numerous development teams in order to guide and consult on design and UI heavy projects, such as upgrading our front-end technologies from PHP to React, and introducing CSS preprocessors to the development teams.

Strong relationship with the product management team, including numerous trips to our US based head office, in order to be a part of product vision development, roadmap creation, and influence design decisions.

I like to think I became core member of staff, helping to organise multiple inter company events like hackathons and social events. I also presented a number of times at brown bag sessions, and ran design workshops.

**Workplace Systems** // UI & Graphic Designer Milton Keynes // January 2015 - July 2016

incentivesmart // Web Designer & Front End Developer
Milton Keynes // April 2013 - December 2014

**Makita UK** // Web & Graphic Designer, & Front End Developer

Milton Keynes // April 2010 - April 2013

Palmiero Design // Web & Graphic Designer, & Front End Developer

Milton Keynes // February 2008 - March 2010

References available on request.